spades-cardgame.com 2016-05-13

# CardGames.io - PRIVACY POLICY

This site, CardGames.io, is created by Rauðás Hugbúnaður ehf ("Red Ace Software LLC"), a small software company in Iceland. Here we will explain what data we store, how we store it, how we use cookies and how our advertising works. 

### Personal information

We do not store any personally identifiable data about users, such as name, location, playing habits or anything else. We have no user accounts so we simply don't have that kind of information available to us. 

### Aggregate data and statistics

We use a third-party service, Google Analytics, to track general usage patterns on our websites. This data includes: 

  * How many visits we get each day
  * How many unique visitors we get each day
  * Where in the world our visitors come from
  * How many games are won by the computer and how many by users
  * What search terms people used to find the page

We have no way of tying any of this data back to individual users. It's only available to us as aggregate statistics. We use this data to understand which games are the most popular, and to improve the games by looking at winning statistics and trying to make the computer players win at least as much as the human players. 

### Log Files

We keep log files of visits to the site. These log files include information about your IP address, the time of your visit, which page was visited and what type of browser was used. We can not tie a visit to any personally identifiable information. 

### Cookies

We use cookies (small bits of information stored on your computer) for a few things: 

  * To remember which options you have chosen for the games.
  * To remember the score between rounds in the games.

### Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

### Game statistics stored on your own computer

This game may keep track of your game statistics, how many times you've won, lost or abandoned a game for example. This data is only stored on your own computer, through a mechanism called [HTML5 Local Storage](http://www.w3.org/TR/webstorage/). This information is never sent away from your computer, so no one other than you has access to it. You can delete this data by going to your browser settings and clearing all data from this website. 

### Contact us

If you would like more information about any of the above, please do not hesitate to contact us at [admin@cardgames.io](mailto:admin@cardgames.io) with any questions or concerns. 

Click here to go back to the frontpage.
